{
    "subject": "resource/Her_Grace_Commands",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Her Grace Commands (German: Ihre Hoheit befiehlt) is a 1931 German romantic comedy film directed by Hanns Schwarz and starring K\u00e4the von Nagy, Willy Fritsch and Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel. It is also translated into the alternative title Her Highness Commands. A hairdresser and a greengrocer fall in love, concealing from each other the truth that they are really a Princess and an army officer in disguise. It premiered in Mannheim on 3 March 1931. A French-language version Princesse, \u00e0 vos ordres! was made simultaneously, also directed by Schwarz but with a different cast. The film was later remade in Hollywood by the Fox Film Corporation as Adorable.",
    "human_readable": "Her Grace Commands is a 1931 German romantic comedy film directed by Hanns Schwarz and starring K\u00e4the von Nagy, Willy Fritsch and Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9264293313026428,
            "question": "Is 'Her Grace Commands' a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195343852043152,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Her Grace Commands'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459145426750183,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Her Grace Commands' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8264603614807129,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Her Grace Commands'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7931544780731201,
            "question": "Name one actor who starred in 'Her Grace Commands'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7859607934951782,
            "question": "What country produced the film 'Her Grace Commands'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808117866516113,
            "question": "Besides romantic comedy, what other genre might 'Her Grace Commands' fit into?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.579412579536438,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Hanns Schwarz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4528641998767853,
            "question": "How might historical context influence our understanding of a 1931 German film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22860969603061676,
            "question": "What is the main theme often explored in romantic comedies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Her Grace Commands is a 1931 German romantic comedy film directed by Hanns Schwarz and starring K\u00e4the von Nagy, Willy Fritsch and Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6978_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might historical context influence our understanding of a 1931 German film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6978_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by Hanns Schwarz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6978_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides romantic comedy, what other genre might 'Her Grace Commands' fit into?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6978_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6978_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe document mentions that \"Her Grace Commands\" stars K\u00e4the von Nagy and Willy Fritsch but doesn't mention Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The information in the documents does support the triple. Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that \"Her Grace Commands is a 1931 German romantic comedy film directed by Hanns Schwarz and starring K\u00e4the von Nagy, Willy Fritsch, and Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel.\" The documents mention Her Grace Commands (originally titled \u201cIhre Hoheit befiehlt\u201d) as a 1931 German comedy film directed by Hanns Schwarz. Although the name of one of the actors is not explicitly mentioned in the provided context, it can be reasonably inferred that Reinhold Sch\u00fcnzel refers to Willy Fritsch based on the context about his acting career and other movies he starred in."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It contradicts information provided about the film starring K\u00e4the von Nagy and Willy Fritsch.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}